const STORE = [
    {
      question: 'Where did George Friedrich Handel spend most his life?',
      answers: [
        'Germany',
        'England',
        'Italy',
        'France'
      ],
      correctAnswer:1
    },
    {
      question:
        'Haydn, Mozart, and Beethoven together make up what historians call "The First Viennese School." What composer is credited with spearheading the "Second" Viennese School?',
      answers: [
        'Arnold Schoenberg',
        'John Williams',
        'David Hasselhoff',
        'Lou Bega'
      ],
      correctAnswer:0
    },
    {
      question:
        'What year did JS Bach die?',
      answers: [
        '1760',
        '2000 B.C.E.',
        '1789',
        '1750'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 3
    },
    {
      question: 'In 1889 the "Paris Exposition Universelle" World Fair brought music from all over the world. One particular style of music influenced young composers like Claude Debussy. What style of music was it?' ,
      answers: [
        'Gamelan',
        'Carnatic Music',
        'Griots',
        'JS Bach'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 0
    },
    {
      question:
        'Who from the composers below is known for prepaired-piano works?',
      answers: [
        'Juliette Clements',
        'John Adams',
        'John Cage',
        'Aaron Copland'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 2
    },
    {
      question: 'Robert Schumann is a well known composer of many works, but it was said his wife was equally as gifted as a composer, and a better pianist. What is her name?',
      answers: [
        'Bjork',
        'Lisa Simpson',
        'Clara Wieck',
        'Michelle Schumann'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 2
    },
    {
      question:
        'This pianist/composer is known for having large hands, and his compositions have to be adapted for people with smaller hands',
      answers: [
        'Sergei Rachmaninoff',
        'Mstislav Rostripovich',
        'Gregor Piatigorsky',
        'Pablo Casals'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 0
    },
    {
      question: 'It was legend that because this violinist was so increidble, they must have sold their soul to the devil',
      answers: [
        'Nadja Salerno-Sonnenberg',
        'Hilary Hahn',
        'Friedrich "Fritz" Kreisler',
        'Niccol√≤ Paganini'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 3
    },
    {
      question: 'Historically, strings on violins, celli, etc were made out of what material?',
      answers: [
        'Ice',
        'Lamb intestine',
        'Horse hair',
        'Copper'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
      question:
        'This Composer was "gently" threatened by Josef Stalin via a newspaper article about one of his new compositions. The accusation being that it was not supportive enough of communism.',
      answers: [
        'Igor Stravinsky',
        'Alexander Scriabin',
        'Alexander Borodin',
        'Dimitri Shostakovich'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 3
    }
  ];